Show me the new stance I just taught you.
Not fast enough. Again!
Just extinguish already.
Monkey clap!
Stop fooling around, Amato!
That was a great move, Tok Sah.
You too can be great someday.
But you have
to take this seriously, Amato.
So teach me, Tok.
Then I can use these moves
against those bullies in school.
Silat should not be used
for violence, Amato.
It is an art meant for self-defense.
Understood, Tok.
Excuse me, Tok.
I'm late to meet with Pian at his house.
Very well. Have a safe journey.
Send my regards to Pian
and his dad, Mr. Aman.
Sure thing, Tok.
Take this!
You call that a fight?
What a waste of time.
Mr. MechaBot, you're right.
You shouldn't waste your time.
Why don't you waste your money
on some boltcorn instead?
What flavor would you like?
Engine oil?
Grease?
Rust?
You think I'm some bolt-munching robot?
I'm a Power Sphera, okay!
I don't eat that junk!
Hey. That hurts.
I get it. A Power Sphera, right?
You don't eat screws,
but I know what you do like to eat.
What's that?
Eat your heart out.
Come on, I can see it on your face.
You're jealous of them, right?
If I had a master,
I could have easily beaten all of them
and freed myself from this prison!
You sure do dream big, sir.
While you're busy
figuring out an escape plan,
why not chew on some boltcorns too?
How about it, sir?
Fine. It's free, right?
Come on! You have to pay for that!
Finally, my search is over!
They thought this prison
would be impossible to detect!
Get ready to attack!
Roger! Form up!
Head for the main deck! Double time!
A little more to the right.
Nearly done, Pian.
Seriously? You came here late
and all you do is goof around.
Sorry. I had silat training earlier.
Besides, I came up with the idea, right?
You just have to build it.
What? Just build it?
Easy for you to say.
Hand me that screwdriver.
Did you find it?
I found it. Here.
How is it looking, Pian?
All done.
I told you it was easy.
The mind-reading cocoa mixer!
Cocoway 3000!
I spent three weeks building this,
so you have to present this.
Hold on, I'm not presenting this
to Mr. Jamie.
It's a group project, isn't it?
It was your idea, but I built it.
So you present it
and I'll be the test dummy.
Fine then.
Okay, class, allow me to present
the Cocoway 3000!
All you have to do is think about it.
Let me guess!
Cocoa-cino?
Iced cocoa?
Hot cocoa…
You look like a lemon cocoa
kind of person.
Done!
This low-sugar cocoa lemon tastes amazing!
It works!
It really can read my mind.
This is an instant A, Amato.
Who knew my simple sketch
would end up becoming a reality?
Good thing you have a friend
who can make sense of your drawings.
I don't think anyone else can do this.
My dad's computer.
Pian, why is the computer beeping?
I have no idea.
What's all this, Pian?
It's my dad's job.
He has been monitoring this comet
for weeks.
He's the first to discover this comet.
He named it after himself, "Comet Aman."
Pian.
How can its trajectory just change?
Something's not quite right here.
Quick, Pian. Show this to your dad.
Dad.
We just finished our design project.
We spent three weeks,
day and night, doing it.
That's great, son. Keep up the good work.
Thanks, Mr. Aman.
If you hadn't lent us
some of your equipment,
we would never have finished the project.
That's right.
Based on the trajectory,
it's heading towards--
I have to report this!
Dad, about my project--
Yes. I'll look at it later, okay?
Something urgent has come up.
Secure the perimeter.
Don't stop until you find him!
How dare you!
It's Grakakus!
Critical damage.
The nearby planet's gravity
is pulling us in!
Fall back and regroup!
Activate the sound dampener
and camouflage.
Relax, don't be sad.
Your dad's just busy.
I'm sure he'll check it out later.
Don't worry, he's going to love it.
It was just bad timing, that's all.
I guess so.
Be careful with the Cocoway 3000.
That's a guaranteed A for us.
Don't worry about that.
Okay Pian, I'll see you in school later.
Bye. Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too. Bye, Amato.
Bob, what's for dinner tonight?
Nasi Padang at Padang.
This Cocoway 3000 is so cool.
I bet Mr. Jamie will love it.
"Well done, Amato and Pian.
I'm giving you an 'A' for your project."
"We worked really hard on it.
How about an A+ instead?"
"I can't give you an A+ for this.
I'll give you triple A+ instead!"
"Well, if you insist.
We'd be happy to accept it."
What in the world is that?
What was that thing that just crashed?
That's strange. I don't see anything.
Did my eyes deceive me?
A crashed spaceship?
What's that?
That hurts.
Someone survived?
A robot?
Who are you?
A talking robot?
Hey, don't come any closer!
Wait, don't shoot!
That was a warning shot.
Come closer if you want to end up
like those trees.
Who dares to attack me?
Oh, no.
He's so huge.
Was it you, MechaBot?
It wasn't me.
I was just following my master's orders.
You have a new master?
-Who's your master?
-You, of course.
Me? Since when?
Just now?
Enough!
You're just looking for trouble,
aren't you?
Is your name "Trouble"?
My name is Troket, not Trouble!
Please don't shoot me!
Look, a flying elephant!
Where?
Flying elephants
are an endangered species.
Run!
Stop following me!
You dare to make me look like a fool?
I'm getting out of here.
Hey! Wait up!
Please don't chase after me,
I didn't do anything wrong!
Hey, what is this thing?
It's just getting in the way.
Hey! That was my design project!
My teacher wants to see it tomorrow.
If we don't lose that guy,
there won't be a tomorrow!
Get back here!
Faster!
Pedal faster!
If you want to pedal faster,
why don't you do it yourself?
But I don't even have legs.
Then do something.
Oh, no!
MechaBot, Mechanize!
What in the world…
What's going on?
My bicycle turned into a motorbike?
Don't you dare run away!
Where did they go?
Wait, slow down! Brake!
It's too late!
What was that noise?
You still haven't found him?
Not yet, General. But…
MechaBot was definitely here recently.
Move out!
Find him and leave no stone unturned!
Yes, General.
My room?
Last night, I was being chased by a robot…
Was I dreaming all this time?
Wake up, Amato.
Why were you sleeping outside last night?
Were you that exhausted
working on that design project?
That robot!
This is an impressive-looking cocoa mixer.
Maybe you can help me
sell cocoa drinks one of these days.
Sure, Dad!
But it's not finished yet.
I still need to iron out some kinks.
I have to go.
Hey, why did you follow me home?
What? Are you for real?
You brought me here, right?
Nonsense. Who are you anyway?
I am MechaBot!
The most powerful destroyer
Power Sphera in this galaxy.
Who are you, kid?
My name is Amato.
My full name is--
Never mind, don't bother.
Nobody cares what your full name is.
Are you serious?
Hey, last night…
Did you actually combine with my bicycle?
A bicycle?
That primitive thing with…
the two wheels?
Of course! What else can you combine with?
Can you combine with a broom?
That hairy thing? No, thank you.
If you can't do it, it's fine.
Who says I can't?
Check this out.
MechaBot, Mechanize!
MechaBlaster!
A high-tech broom.
What are you doing?
That's not how you use me.
Then what's the right way?
Dad's going to be so mad. But…
this is so cool!
Being your master sure has its perks.
Wait a minute.
When did you become my master?
Don't you remember last night?
You have a new master?
-Who's your master?
-You, of course!
Me? Since when?
Just now?
Hey, that doesn't count.
Okay. If that doesn't count,
then how do I make it so?
How does someone
actually become your master?
It's not as easy as you think.
In order to become my master,
you have to defeat me.
Seize this Mechanizer
and press the confirmation button.
This button?
Hey, not that one!
It's that button.
This button?
Hey, don't!
Yes! Finally, I am your new master!
That's not how it works.
You still have to defeat me!
I did defeat you. I used my wits.
Isn't that right?
What does this button do?
Nothing. That button's for ordering food.
Really? Let's try ordering some food then.
No--
What? MechaBot?
That button is not for ordering food.
That is the truth button.
The truth button?
Why are you suddenly so polite?
This is how I was designed, master.
That button forces me
to speak nothing but the truth.
That's handy.
Okay, let me ask you. Who is your master?
You are my master.
You managed to defeat me
using your high level of intellect.
So it's true.
It's a good thing
you're not that smart then.
I dropped out of high school, master.
That figures.
Hey, what did you do just now?
Nothing. I just ordered food, that's all.
Well, that was fast.
There you are.
-Oh, no…
Do you have any idea how many rooftops
I had to destroy in order to find you?
Where did my roof go?
Follow your master!
You're not my master!
I'm going to destroy you
and your new master too!
Thanks for recognizing me
as his new master.
You're not my master!
How many times do I have to say it?
I'm not your master, is it?
Don't listen to what I say.
You are my master, master.
I know, right?
Hi, I'm Amato. MechaBot's new master.
Quiet!
You be quiet.
Only my master can command me to be quiet.
Prepare to meet your doom!
Let's run, master.
MechaBot!
Combine with this to become a jetpack.
Okay. MechaBot, Mechanize!
MechaJetpack!
Pretty good idea, kid.
What was all that noise?
Being your master is so much fun!
Fun? Fun for you, maybe.
Pian!
Amato?
Amato!
Hey, watch it! Can't you fly properly?
You think you can run from me?
Amato!
MechaBot!
Hey, do something!
What do you want me to do?
Save me, quick!
Try being more specific.
Save you how, exactly?
Just save me, okay?
I don't want to die!
If you fall to your death,
then I can find a new master, right?
I got it, you can combine with me.
He figured it out. Fine.
MechaBot…
What bot? Hurry up!
…Mechanize!
Who is that?
Oh, no,
that hurts.
You can combine with me?
Just this once, I had no choice!
What is that?
-Grandma, look at that.
-What is that?
I'm doomed.
You can't hide from me!
Take this!
Missile barrage!
Run!
Get out!
MechaBot!
Mechanize!
You turned this car door
into a high-tech shield.
My Mechanize power is impressive, right?
Help! Help us!
Mara!
Mom!
Amato! Get up, Amato!
You're finished!
What am I going to do?
There, Mechanize that thing!
I will destroy you!
MechaBot, Mechanize!
Fire!
No!
We did it!
We won!
Who are you?
I'm…
Mecha--
Amato!
Mechamato?
-McTomato?
No, it's Mechamato.
Okay, we should get moving.
Let's go!
Goodbye!
I love our new name. Mechamato!
Wait. This suit has a jetpack, right?
No.
That's got to hurt.
Not again.
Oh, no…
That hurts.
That tomato boy has a rock-hard head.
How could I have lost to that puny kid?
Prisoner Troket has been located.
Who are you?
My Power Sphera collection…
that's still incomplete!
Where is the MechaBot Power Sphera?
Spectre,
Vendetta,
Omega,
reporting in.
General, we have been attacked.
What?
Who dares to damage my droid?
The identity of the attacker
is not in our database.
So he must be from this planet.
We managed to repel the attack.
Troket has also been secured,
along with another prisoner.
Troket, Prisoner 091, Class A, and--
Prisoner 159, Bagogo.
A model prisoner, sir.
The perfect candidate to be your in-law.
Come on, what's with the restraints?
They have information about MechaBot.
Tell me what you know.
I know so many things, good sir.
I know how to read,
I can do maths, subtraction, addition,
even algebra.
What are you babbling on about?
I'm asking you about MechaBot!
MechaBot?
He's an old buddy of mine.
We even ate a screw together once.
I can tell you anything you want to know,
for a price, of course.
Pay you?
Of course. Good intel isn't free.
I'm not some public Wi-Fi service.
I don't do things for free.
We have a comedian over here.
Hey, what are you doing--
That hurts, sir!
Don't hurt me! Please let me go!
Now then, do you have
any information for me?
Mecha…
MechaBot has a new master.
A boy named Amato.
Amato?
Yes. I saw it myself,
he combined with that Amato boy!
He dares to use MechaBot.
Looks like I'll have to crush that boy,
just like I crushed his previous master.
Get in, MechaBot.
I need to tell Pian about this.
Please pick up.
Who's Pian?
My best friend.
Pian! You saw me flying, right?
It was so cool!
-I combined with that alien robot and we--
-What? Alien robot?
Is that Mr. Aman?
Where's Pian?
Pian went out.
You were saying something about a robot?
It's nothing.
Can you ask Pian
to call me back later? Bye!
Here's a video footage from a witness…
…that caused traffic jams
on the main road.
Good morning, Dad, Mom.
Good morning.
I made your favorite dish this morning.
Thank you, Mom.
Sit here and be quiet.
Yes, I was there at the scene.
There were explosions everywhere!
And if I'm not mistaken,
his name was Mc… McTomato!
Are you sure it wasn't
the vigilante Maskmana?
Absolutely sure?
No! Maskmana is blue,
this one was all red, like a tomato!
-She's right! It was McTomato!
-It's Mechamato!
Authorities still don't know
who was behind the attack
on the bridge
and will continue to investigate.
I'm just an automatic cocoa machine.
Yes. And that concludes our update
on the robot attack
at Seri Dua Bridge.
Now, back to the studio.
Thank you, Ravi J.
The public is advised to be cautious.
Please report any suspicious activities
to the authorities
and avoid acting on your own.
What's that about?
They said there was a robot attack.
That sounds dangerous if it's true.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Maskmana will protect us.
Weren't you paying attention?
Don't act alone like Maskmana.
Am I right, Amato?
Right, Dad! Gosh, I'm late.
I have a design project presentation
this morning.
I'll get going now.
Did you take your lunch money?
I did, Mom. Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
MechaBot,
if Dad and Mom ever find out about you,
I'll be in trouble.
What am I going to do?
Just act normal, that's all.
That's your solution? Act normal?
Bula? Bili?
Hey, don't say a word.
Where are you headed, Amato?
I'm heading to school.
Aren't you going to school?
Only dummies go to school.
I'm already smart,
so why do I need to go to school?
Indeed. You are right, boss.
You got straight A's
in your mid-year report card.
Right, Bili?
Do you want me to tutor you?
Since we're friends,
I'll only charge you RM10 per minute.
How dare they?
Don't!
Don't what?
I don't have that much.
How about RM5?
Since we're friends, all right.
What a loser.
RM3, RM4, RM5…
50 cents. Here.
What's this for?
That's your change.
My tuition fee is only 5 ringgit.
Be sure to spend it wisely.
-Okay…
-You're so generous, boss.
Why didn't you stand up to them?
I could've taught them a lesson!
I can't, my master forbids me.
Besides, we have to be careful.
Otherwise, everyone will find out
about you!
Excuses.
That's enough.
Just remember your job for today.
Become Cocoway 3000, got it?
Hey, Amato. Good morning.
Deep, good morning to you too.
Have you seen Pian?
No, I don't think he's here yet.
You finished it!
Your design project looks really cool!
Thank you.
Did you finish yours?
Of course, I finished it.
Behold, my genius invention.
Speed!
Split!
Combs!
They're just regular combs.
Hey, no they're not.
These combs are revolutionary!
Innovative!
Check this out. See?
With twice the number of combs,
you can cut the amount of time needed
to comb your hair by 50%!
Whatever you say, Deep.
You can just comb your hair
in 30 seconds only.
Where's Pian? Class is about to start.
There he is.
Pian!
Amato!
You were awesome yesterday!
Where did you get that high-tech jetpack?
Yes, that's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
-Okay, sit down. Yesterday--
-All rise.
-Good morning, sir.
Good morning!
Okay, sit down.
Before we proceed
with the design presentation,
I would like to introduce
your new classmate.
-What should I do?
-New student?
Hey, stop that.
Is that a boy or a girl?
That's…
the girl from yesterday.
Yesterday?
Mara, please introduce yourself.
Hi, my name is Tamara,
you can call me Mara.
Do you know her?
Amato! Pian!
Yes, sir!
Are you ready to present
your design project?
Absolutely.
Come, Amato.
Pian, wait…
You can sit over there, Mara.
Okay, sir.
Presenting
our automatic cocoa mixing machine,
the Cocoway 3000…
What is this thing, Amato?
It looks different.
I made some upgrades to it.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Give us a demonstration then.
How does it work?
It's okay, I'll do it.
Okay!
We start by adding some cocoa powder.
Next, we pour in some hot water…
and stir it.
What? Is that all?
I have no idea.
Wait, what am I even watching?
We're not done yet.
Next we…
Open your mouth!
Pour water into the cocoa machine.
Hot! It's hot!
Finally, we give it a few shakes…
and it's ready to drink!
The Cocoway 3000…
Be careful, it's very hot…
What do you think, sir?
I think you both…
F… A… I… L!
Pass?
Fail!
What am I going to tell my dad, Amato?
We failed.
Just tell him, MechaBot.
Back my story up.
I'm just an automatic cocoa mixer,
Cocoway 3000.
Yes! I passed!
Speed, split, combs!
Yes!
Yes! I passed!
Good for him.
MechaBot, say something!
Why you…
I know that we're best friends, Amato.
But this whole "robot" story of yours
is putting a strain on our friendship.
I forgot about this thing.
Hey! Wait!
He can talk?
Please don't press that button.
Well? Show him your Mechanize power!
Make-up nice?
That's right.
He'll make you up so you'll look nice.
What's make-up nice?
It's Mechanize! Like this!
MechaBot, Mechanize!
MechaBlaster!
Check this out!
He can change a broom into a blaster?
I told you so.
You shouldn't have doubted me.
That's amazing!
Now, Mechanize with this bicycle.
Do you think I'm your robot slave?
No, thank you.
It's okay, Pian.
Everyone has their limits.
Maybe that's all he's capable of.
I guess so.
Even my dad says
what's most important is that we try.
It's okay if we fail.
Hey, I never fail!
Feast your eyes!
MechaBot, Mechanize!
MechaBike!
Impressive!
He can turn into a cool motorbike!
I know, right?
But you can't tell anyone
about this, okay?
Tell anyone about what?
Mara?
You seem angry.
What are you two up to?
Nothing. Just taking this bike
out for a spin.
Yes.
This is just an ordinary motorbike.
Not related to a red robot at all.
Cut it out.
What are you doing here, Mara?
I want you to replace my wheelchair!
Why would he do that?
He pushed me when we were on the bridge.
Pushed you?
You mean I saved you.
But that wasn't me anyway.
You can't fool me.
You're that McTomato, right?
It's Mechamato, okay?
Not McTomato.
What robot is that?
Oh, no!
MechaBot, surrender yourself!
Don't!
Oh, no…
My hand…
Eliminate any opposition.
You can't bring guns to a fistfight.
That's not fair!
Hop on, Amato!
There's more of them?
MechaBot, let's go!
Transform into McTomato!
It's Mechamato!
It is with great pleasure that I,
Mayor Andy,
proudly officiate
this year's Decorative Trishaw Tournament!
Long live Mayor Andy!
Keep it up, Mayor Andy!
And coming up shortly,
we will be entertained
by a special performance
from BBB!
-BBB?
Oh, no!
Mechanize with that piece of scrap!
Did he just call that scrap?
MechaBot, Mechanize!
MechaBeca!
Get in, Amato!
Go, MechaBot!
What are you going to do
with my trishaw, kid?
This must be Amato's new design project!
Is this your trishaw? Mind if I borrow it?
Of course you can, kid.
But go easy on the pedals, will you?
Watch out, kid!
Slow down, kid!
I'm not married yet!
Yes, MechaBot!
Oh, no.
I think this is my stop, kid.
Let's go, Amato!
My goodness!
Let me off, kid!
Look out, Amato!
Hey!
That's a dead end, kid!
MechaBot!
MechaBeca, Flight Mode!
My trishaw!
This is the owner of the trishaw!
Yes! How are you? Thank you!
He's not answering
any of my calls or my messages.
Pian, Mr. Aman Askandar
is your dad, right?
Yes, how did you know?
I did some research
on this town before moving here.
Maskmana has been spotted
around this town too, right?
That's right.
Maskmana is a local hero.
Cool, right?
Don't you think it's odd?
Maskmana wears a very high-tech suit.
So?
And your dad is a pioneer
of cutting-edge technology.
You must think Maskmana
is actually my dad, right?
Here, take a look.
They're both in the same picture?
We're finally safe.
They're no longer chasing us.
Chasing us?
They're chasing you, right?
What do they want with you?
Nothing. They're just jealous of me.
I'm serious.
It's true.
They hate me for my good looks.
So you don't want to answer me
when I ask nicely?
Don't!
0001, counter 1.
How can I help you?
Who were those robots?
Why were they after you?
Those were General Grakakus' robots,
tasked with hunting me down
so he can use me for evil deeds.
Grakakus?
Yes, Grakakus.
An obsessive and aggressive collector
of armor-type Power Spheras,
especially handsome ones like me.
Please.
So what is a Power Sphera?
Power Spheras are high-tech robots
with the ability to grant powers
to its master.
So your power is Mechanizing?
Correct, master.
How long have you been
on the run from Grakakus?
A long time, master.
Since he killed my old master.
He killed your old master?
Yes, that's why I willingly surrendered
myself to the Space Prison.
To avoid being detected.
But I'm your master now.
Correct. If Grakakus wants me,
he would have to kill you first.
Kill me?
Don't worry.
The probability
of it happening is only 99%.
Think positive.
Think positive, you say?
Yes.
My previous master
always taught me to be positive,
right until the day he was killed.
I'm doomed.
Evade, MechaBot!
Brace for impact
and certain death, master.
Oh, no…
That hurts.
Who shot at us?
Where do you think you're going?
You again?
What do you want now?
Don't ask me. You should ask…
MechaBot, at last, we meet again!
General Grakakus?
Don't be afraid, MechaBot.
You're MechaBot's new master?
Yes, stay back!
Time to die!
Out of the way, Amato!
MechaBot, Mechanize!
Okay!
You'll never take MechaBot!
How dare you use him!
Watch out, Amato!
Show yourself!
Do you think you can hide from me?
Find something to Mechanize.
What are you doing?
Stop controlling my movements.
These are so sharp.
What's wrong with you humans?
None of these are useful.
Stop hiding.
It's hopeless for you.
What kind of trash is this?
MechaBot, Mechanize!
Here's something to remember me by.
This kid!
How do you like my toilet paper bomb?
Oh, no,
that hurts.
My systems…
Amato, over there!
Going somewhere?
MechaBot, Mechanize!
Fire, MechaBot!
MechaBot,
what's wrong?
Move, MechaBot.
You have lost!
Now, surrender MechaBot to me.
I may have lost,
but you…
will never get MechaBot!
Goodbye, my friend--
Master!
You won't escape me this time!
You dare to cause trouble here.
In the name of God.
Maskmana?
Get ready.
You're about to meet your match!
You…
You were the one who destroyed my droid!
Advance, drones!
Come on then, it's your move!
You'll pay for that!
Attack!
Shield!
Push!
You've got some fight in you.
Amato…
Where do you think you're going?
Take this!
My eyes!
Return to me.
Curse you!
I won't stop until I find you!
Look at that view.
You're so lucky
you get to come up here anytime you want.
Lucky?
I'm at home more often than not.
Dad?
Are you there?
It's so dark.
It's so huge.
What a collection.
Looks like he's not here.
Pian?
Dad!
What are you doing here?
Looking for you.
You weren't answering
any of my calls or messages.
Where were you?
I was in the lab and I forgot my phone.
Why do you ask?
We were hoping you could help us
find Amato, Mr. Aman.
This is Mara. Our new friend.
Hi, Mr. Aman. How are you?
I'm fine.
Amato, right?
You just missed him.
Is he okay, Dad?
Was anybody chasing him or anything?
I don't think so.
In that case,
sorry to bother you, Mr. Aman.
Wait a minute.
Let me take a look at that.
It's not as bad as it looks.
This is a temporary fix.
Drop by again soon, okay?
Thank you, Mr. Aman.
You're welcome.
Bob,
please send these kids home.
What about you?
I have some work to do.
I'll be home soon, okay?
Send them home, okay?
Yes, Mr. Aman.
Where am I?
You're awake, Amato?
Tok Sah?
MechaBot…
Where's MechaBot?
Lie down, Amato. You're injured.
MechaBot.
What happened to MechaBot?
Maskmana's mask?
You…
You're Maskmana?
It's good that you're awake, Amato.
Here's the medicine.
Mr. Aman?
Is Tok Sah…
Maskmana?
No.
But that mask…
Is it you?
It's not just him.
We…
are all Maskmana.
Mayor Andy?
Try not to move too much.
Here, drink this.
It's so bitter. What is this?
A combination of modern
and traditional medicine.
Drink up, Amato.
Were you the one who saved me earlier?
Yes.
Thank you, Tok.
If you hadn't been there--
Don't waste time on the what-ifs.
Be thankful that I arrived just in time.
Yes, Tok.
How is it possible
for three people to be Maskmana?
By using this.
We take turns using this suit,
when the need arises.
The suit is made from Spheranium,
which is a type of metal
that's very hard to find.
That looks like pieces from a spaceship.
Yes.
That's why Mr. Aman
was tracking the comet.
But who would have known,
that the comet
hurtling towards Earth was a spaceship.
Using AI and machine-learning technology,
the suit can learn from its users.
That means…
The more people use the suit,
the more it learns from them.
A self-learning suit?
Yes. Asah was chosen
for his skills in martial arts
and Andy was chosen
for his tactical insight.
And also
to help with the cover-up.
One suit,
with multiple users?
No wonder nobody knows
Maskmana's true identity.
Come here, Amato.
That's a lot of robots.
These are just a few.
There are many more out there.
If that's the case,
you're going to need my help.
No, Amato.
Haven't you learned anything
from last night?
This is not a game!
You can't go around playing the hero!
But I have MechaBot's Mechanize power.
And you think that makes you a hero?
Amato,
a hero isn't born from power.
A hero is born
from courage
and responsibility.
We have been working hard
to keep this operation a secret.
But you led those robots
into crowded places!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
What you did on the bridge that day,
was that an accident too?
You have to be more responsible, Amato.
MechaBot wields incredible power.
And he's yours, right?
Yes, Tok.
But it's a pity
that it synchronized
with such a foolish kid!
I need to go.
There are some things
I need to take care of.
Don't take what Mayor Andy
said personally.
His words may be harsh, but he means well.
If it wasn't for that masked clown…
MechaBot would have been mine!
Come to me,
my Power Sphera collection!
It's time to show them,
the real Grakakus!
Just imagine,
if I could Mechanize all of this!
Prepare for takeoff!
How did you get hurt?
What kind of silat moves
were you practicing?
He's fine.
Kids get carried away sometimes.
Thank goodness
you were at Tok Sah's place.
What if it happened at a place
where no one could help?
It's just a scratch, Mom.
Yes.
I am currently with Mayor Andy.
Congratulations on the success
of the Decorative Trishaw Competition
yesterday.
Yes. Thank you to everyone
-who attended yesterday.
-What a phony.
-There was a variety
-Smiling for the cameras while on TV.
of decorative trishaws
on display yesterday.
Along with a special performance
of a robot chase scene!
Yes, correct.
The robots were from Destar Corporation,
with Mr. Aman himself as the owner.
And the flying trishaw,
was that a gimmick or--
There is no "or".
It's absolutely a gimmick!
We couldn't have done it without…
Mr. Sasau here.
That old man from yesterday?
Mr. Sasau
is the Decorative Trishaw champion.
Are you kidding me?
Why'd you turn the TV off?
No reason, Dad.
I'm going to hang out with Pian for a bit.
You're going out in that condition?
I won't be long, Mom.
Where am I?
Amato.
Where are you, Amato?
That…
That's a piece of metal
from the spaceship.
Yes, MechaBot.
You're Maskmana?
What are you doing?
Don't worry,
I just want to fix you, and…
separate you from Amato.
What?
You think Amato
deserves to wield your power?
You don't, right?
Your power is too great
and too dangerous for a boy like Amato.
But
I've already synchronized with Amato.
Is it even possible to--
It has to be.
If not,
Amato's life will always be in danger.
Any system can be bypassed.
I just need some time
to decode your system.
You want to use me?
Yes.
We need all the firepower
we can get to defeat Grakakus.
Aman, do you think
he will accept our decision?
Whether or not he can accept it
is not the issue, Asah.
Okay, Bili. Let's find a victim to bully.
Amato, that's dangerous.
What are you doing, Mara?
Where's MechaBot?
He was damaged.
Damaged? What happened yesterday?
You called and said everything was fine.
He's being repaired.
Who would have the ability
to repair MechaBot?
Maskmana.
Maskmana? Are you for real?
It's true.
He helped me defeat the robots yesterday.
Lucky you!
Did you manage to get his autograph?
You're silly.
I'm sure he was too busy fighting
to ask for an autograph.
What a wasted opportunity, Amato.
Big deal. Just get one from--
Get one from who?
No one.
Hi, Amato.
What are you up to?
-Bula and Bili?
You know what day it is today, right?
Teacher's Day?
That's incorrect.
Today is the day you get bullied.
Are you sure?
Try checking your schedule again.
Of course I'm sure. Show him, Bili.
Two days ago it was Deep,
yesterday was Ah Wang,
the two of you get today
and tomorrow.
Why do we get two days?
Friends get a discount.
I didn't know bullies had schedules.
Of course.
In order to be a successful bully,
we need to have discipline
and strong organizational skills.
Amato,
use your silat skills.
I wish I could use,
but Tok Sah forbids me
from using silat for violence.
Using what for what?
Nothing.
Bula, look,
a swimming goat.
Where? I've never seen
a swimming goat before.
Boss, Amato's getting away!
I can't use violence,
but I can use my wits.
Catch me if you can.
How dare you. Go and get him, Bili.
We're safe.
Thank goodness Amato lured them away.
What kind of bullies are these?
He's not over here, boss.
Where are you hiding, Amato?
Come out so we can bully you.
Let's check at the front, boss.
Help!
What are you doing?
We're supposed to be bullies,
not bully-victims.
This robot again?
Target acquired.
Target is trying to escape.
No visual on MechaBot.
No MechaBot?
Eliminate the boy
and stop at nothing
until you find MechaBot!
Unable to locate the target.
Looking for me?
That's…
-What is that noise?
-The track has been shot.
What happened?
Keep firing!
And keep firing until he reveals himself!
Sam, dear.
What's that up there?
It's just an airshow, darling.
Stop! Stop that train!
The track has collapsed, darling!
Where?
Where, my dear Samdol?
Oh, no.
Dad!
What just happened?
Maskmana?
Everybody, get off the train.
He's here, Amato.
Finally, there you are!
Where's MechaBot?
Why is he not with you?
Hurry, drones!
Amato! What's his status?
You again?
Bad aliens!
How dare you, child!
Stop!
If you're looking for MechaBot,
I have him.
He's with you?
How's the progress on MechaBot?
85%.
I'm nearly there!
Prepare the--
Surrender MechaBot to me now.
Andy!
Are you okay?
We're so high up!
So this is where you'd like to be buried?
I need you, Asah.
When will MechaBot be ready?
Nearly there. Hold on a bit longer, Aman!
Tok Sah! MechaBot!
Activate, Kerisis Drones!
Tok Sah?
You'll regret coming here!
You think I'm afraid of your toys?
Drones!
Keris Kerisis Mode!
Take this!
You dare come here,
now pay the price.
You think you've won?
Fire!
Aman!
Don't move, Aman.
Your spine is fractured!
I…
I can't let him--
Weak!
Pitiful!
You're no match for me.
Hand MechaBot over,
now!
Over my dead body.
Only yours?
Your body's not the only one
I'm stepping over,
but…
I will step over their bodies as well.
-Help!
-What happened?
Pian!
That's Maskmana!
-Help us!
-Help!
Asah, we need you here now!
Asah…
MechaBot has been separated.
Hey, MechaBot. You're nearly fixed.
That's not what that means.
Then what does it mean?
That means he's being separated from you.
Separated?
What do you mean, Tok?
You…
You're no longer MechaBot's master.
Is that true, MechaBot?
It's true, Amato.
They managed
to bypass my system.
But…
Sorry, Amato.
We need MechaBot.
There's no other weapon
that can defeat Grakakus.
But you can't do this.
MechaBot is my robot.
You can't separate him from me!
We have no other choice, Amato.
It's too dangerous
to let you be his master.
But
you said it yourself
I have to be responsible.
If something dangerous happens,
I can't keep running away
from that responsibility.
But
this isn't a game, Amato.
Lives are in danger.
I'm not playing around, Tok.
I've seen what happened
to MechaBot's previous master.
Goodbye, my friend--
And then?
Do you want to end up
like my old master too, Amato?
I don't know
what's going to happen, MechaBot.
But I know that you're my robot.
You're my responsibility!
But I…
I don't want you to be my master.
Why not?
I'm…
afraid of losing another friend.
Afraid?
Why didn't you just say that
from the beginning?
Afraid of losing a friend!
Not other things!
What's going on with these two?
The bad robot is a softie on the inside.
What are you talking about?
I've only got wires on the inside!
Why did you abort it?
You really are Amato's robot.
You two were meant for each other.
Tok!
Thank you for not taking
MechaBot away from me.
Time to fulfill
your responsibility, Amato.
You have to stop Grakakus.
Yes, Tok.
Let's go, MechaBot.
MechaBot, Mechanize!
Where are you, Grakakus?
I'm going to teach you a lesson!
Amato?
Where did Grakakus go?
I bet he ran away. Coward.
Coward, you say?
I'm General Grakakus!
You think I'm afraid of a kid like you?
Why…
Why this kid, Asah?
That's Amato! Save us, Amato!
Help, McTomato!
Pian! Mara!
Maskmana?
I thought we separated MechaBot? Why--
Put your trust in Amato!
Good.
You've brought MechaBot to me.
Get over here!
Are you just going to dodge everything?
I'm trying here!
What can this kid even do, Asah?
I hope you made the right call, Asah.
MechaBot, Mechanize!
Why out of all things,
did he choose a mop?
Is that it?
Make sure he's squeaky clean, Amato.
You fools!
Close your eyes, MechaBot!
I'll control our movements by myself!
Trust me!
I'm going to make you regret that.
Regret?
Who? Me?
Just close your eyes!
Is that really my friend out there?
Give up, before you lose!
That's right!
If you don't, we'll keep beating you up!
Don't be so confident.
Drop them!
Hey, let us go!
Don't let us go!
What…
What are we going to do?
Grandma!
Ucu!
Help!
Did you really think you could save them?
Oh, no!
Pian!
No, Aman!
Your spine!
MechaBot, Mechanize!
Get up!
Are you…
Are you okay, Pian?
Maskmana knows my name?
Dad?
Thank you, Amato.
Watch out, Mara!
Get over here!
Look at me, MechaBot!
It hurts!
Time to separate yourself, MechaBot,
from this kid!
Now,
you just need to die!
Amato!
MechaBot!
Goodbye, my friend--
Amato…
Your master is dead!
Finally,
you will be mine, Power Sphera MechaBot!
Witness, the perfect form
of General Grakakus!
MechaBot, Mechanize!
Don't!
Why is nothing happening?
I said Mechanize!
That's a long drop!
My friend.
Amato is still alive!
-MechaBot! Help!
-Amato!
Why are you not dead yet?
MechaBot, Mechanize!
What did he Mechanize with?
Mega Mechamato!
You're still using him?
Hand MechaBot over to me!
You want MechaBot, right?
Come and get him!
Take this!
-How do you like that?
We need to fly, MechaBot!
Where do you think you're going?
Close your eyes, MechaBot.
No need. We can defeat him together!
We are…
-Mechamato!
You missed!
Brace yourself
for the Monkey Clap!
Use the Kerisis Drones, Amato!
MechaBot…
Mechanize!
MechaKerisis!
Take this, Grakakus!
General!
Fire!
It can't be…
You've lost, Grakakus!
I am
General Grakakus!
There is no way I would ever lose to you!
Lose to me?
No, not to me.
You'll lose to that.
We did it, Amato!
-Right?
Help, Amato!
Amato!
We need to help them!
Let's go!
Are you all okay?
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Have faith, Aman.
Everything happens for a reason.
Right?
How is your dad, Pian?
Mr. Aman is paralyzed.
What?
It's true, Amato.
I'm sorry, Mr. Aman.
Pian…
You're sorry?
I'm the one who should thank you.
If it wasn't for you…
things would have been much worse.
But it looks like you'll have
to shoulder the responsibility
of being Maskmana's successor--
There's no need.
Asah and I are still here.
Amato has proven himself, Andy.
We need to place our trust in him.
There's a robot disturbance in town.
I'll head out.
It's okay, Mayor Andy.
We'll deal with it.
Come on, MechaBot!
Why aren't you moving?
Today's a Saturday, right?
It's my day off.
Hey!
Heroes don't get days off.
What kind of people work weekends?
Okay, smart mouth.
Well-mannered Mode!
Don't!
Yes, master. How can I help you?
Do robots get days off?
They do, master.
However, I'm a servant robot.
Servants don't get days off, master.
I thought so. In that case…
MechaBot, Mechanize!
Okay, I'll Mechanize right away.
Excuse me.
MechaBot…
Mechanize.
Which robot would you like?
Rover, Fido, or Spot?
If you take them all,
I'll throw in a Troket free of charge.
Hey!
It's one thing to try to sell me,
but you're giving me away for free?
Hey, don't take it personally.
It's just business.
Yes, sir.
What? Come on, there is no such thing
as a friend's discount.
We were never even friends before.
Please hold for one moment.
I've just got some walk-in customers.
Yes, hello, sirs.
How may I help you today?
Who's this little alien here?